yeah it it is super exciting to be out
there and I think this is this is very
much a mission that is anchored in the
future right we're thinking about
where's the world going we're looking to
evolve it with the system and so I think
what you can expect from us is just a
lot of collaboration a lot of
conversation and a decent amount of
experimentation on it we hope and
hopefully even this year to launch some
products that you can try in beta form
you can give us the opinion on you can
work with us to again reshape and figure
out what is correct get a little bit of
mileage of what actually works with
today's technology what doesn't so a lot
of the things that we expect to do in
this podcast and you'll see on our blog
you'll see in our newsletter is just
really boosting the conversation around
this domain and in the background we're
working on trying to build a a product
platform that learns from those and that
helps both fulfill some of these
promises but also try out some of these
ideas and see what works